http://www.hastingstribune.com/site/privacy.html

Goodfellows
Privacy Policy for www.hastingstribune.comThis privacy policy sets out how the Hastings Tribune uses and protects any information that you give the Hastings Tribune when you use this website.The Hastings Tribune is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.The Hastings Tribune may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from May 7, 2018.What we collectWe may collect the following information:name and job titlecontact information including email addressdemographic information such as postcode, preferences and interestsother information relevant to customer surveys and/or offersWhat we do with the information we gatherWe require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:Internal record keeping.We may use the information to improve our products and services.We may periodically send promotional emailsabout new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided. SecurityWe are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure,we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.How we use cookiesA cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.Links to other websitesOur website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.Controlling your personal informationIn addition to the described above, we and third parties may use cookies and other tracking technologies to facilitate serving relevant ads to you. For example, these technologies help us determine whether you have seen a particular advertisement before, tailor ads to you if you have visited our site before, and avoid sending you duplicate advertisements.In addition to disabling cookies and other tracking technologies, you may opt-out of receiving targeted advertising from participating ad networks, audience segment providers, ad serving vendors, and other service providers by visiting http://optout.networkadvertising.org/?c=1#!/ or http://optout.aboutads.info/?c=2#!/If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at webmaster@hastingstribune.com. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
Goodfellows
#LocalFoodToGo
#LocalFoodToGo
Updates from Local Advertisers
Check out our Affordable Print and Online Subscription Rates!Affordable rates for:
Adams, Clay, Nuckolls and Webster Counties, as well as the towns of Doniphan and Giltner, Fillmore, Franklin, Kearney, Thayer Counties, Smith, Jewell Counties (Kansas)
Subscribe
Most Popular
Articles
Images
Videos
Commented
ArticlesHastings print business stays a family traditionVirus claims another life in Adams County2 killed, 2 critically injured in Omaha house explosionNiobrara woman arrested after Norfolk man stabbed to deathDally's home of a 'bazillion' sandwichesSchmidt follows footsteps of familyCalico Cottage a one-stop shop for quiltersVirus claims three more lives in Adams County, one in Franklin County
Images
Videos
CommentedSorry, there are no recent results for popular commented articles.
